(Leonard:)The interface is pretty simple.
You put your horizontal X-coordinate here,
vertical Y-coordinate here.
(Leonard:)When you're happy with those,
press this button.
(Penny:)Got it.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you'll never guess
who I just found online. Hey.
- Nice shot.
- Eh, his giant head did most of the work.
(Sheldon:)Very mature.
You're lucky I'm out of Silly String.
(Sheldon:)As I was saying, Leonard,
you'll never guess who I just found online.
(Sheldon:)- Professor Proton.
- You're kidding.
(Leonard:)- He's still alive?
- Yes.
- Who's Professor Proton?
- He was the host of this great... Hey.
Yes. Sorry, tell me about Professor Proton.
Professor Proton hosted my favorite
science show when I was a child.
(Sheldon:)I never missed an episode.
(Sheldon:)He demonstrated scientific principles
using everyday objects.
(Leonard:)It was pretty cool.
Aw. It's so cute when you use
the word "cool" wrong.
Like when kids say "pasghetti."
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord. Leonard, look.
(Sheldon:)He's still available for parties and events.
(Sheldon:)- We should hire him.
- Hire him to do what?
(Sheldon:)Whatever we want.
Hang out, do experiments...
(Sheldon:)...make him take 12 pictures with us
so we can make a calendar.
It would be awesome to hang out with him.
I just used "awesome" wrong, didn't I?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm e-mailing him right now.
- Do you remember his old theme song?
- Of course I do.
(Together:)Grab your goggles, put your lab coat on
(Together:)Here he comes, Professor Proton